And one of those Debeers diamond
commercials came on and it used to end
with
>> a diamond is forever.
And the girl I was dating looked over at
me and she was like, "You know, a
diamond is forever."
[laughter]
I was like, "I know." So is styrofoam
actually. [laughter]
I haven't talked to my wife in about 8
hours, actually, which is uh at this
point a little bit longer than I like to
leave her alone with her thoughts. Uh
cuz we're still starting out. So my plan
is basically just every morning I wake
up and convince her once again this is a
really good idea
and we can't return our wedding gifts.
So [laughter]
hopefully it all works out. I love being
married though. It's great. It's like
dating with consequences. It's uh
[laughter]
it's a lot of fun. And people ask me
like why did you get married? Why'd you
propose to your wife? And there are a
lot of reasons definitely but really
chief among them is that my wife is
smarter than I am. And if you can date
somebody smarter, I highly recommend
doing that. It is [laughter] it's a
fantastic way to go. Just surround
yourself with smart people in general if
you can. I know dumb people are fun. I
am not not going to deny that. And if
you're dumb, thank you. It's
really entertaining for everybody else,
but
but if you swap out your dumb friends
for smart friends, it's a lot less
funny, but you're going to cut way down
on the number of text messages you get
at 2 in the morning. I guarantee you
that nobody asked for $200 that you
can't ask about or anything. That's
gone. So, and if you can date somebody
smarter than you, I highly recommend
doing that. As a matter of fact, if
you're dating somebody here tonight, uh,
one of you is smarter than the other.
That's just a fact. No two people get
together that are the exact same level
of intelligence. One person is going to
be smart. As a matter of fact, clap if
you think you're the smart person in
YOUR RELATIONSHIP. [cheering]
BOY, WAS THAT a mixed bag. That was a I
like there were a handful of people out
there. They're like, "Nope, the smart
person doesn't clap right here." I know
that this is
this is a trap. [laughter]
That was so interesting to watch. You
had I saw some couples where both people
were clapping. [laughter]
Oh, all right. No, we're not done
talking about this, actually.
>> [laughter]
>> We're going to talk about this on the
way home. As a matter of fact, I also
saw some couples where people were
definitely together and neither person
was clapping,
which is cute cuz that can mean one of
two things. There's option A, which
could be like, "Hey, I'm not clapping
because I think that you're SP." Oh,
this way. You're not clapping cuz you
think that I'm Well, that's just
Do you want to get some gelato on the
way home? Cuz this is Do you want to
adopt a puppy? We're wonderful.
[laughter]
That's possible. That could exist as
option A, but you have to admit could
also be option B, which is like, "Hey,
I'm not clapping because I think you're
Oh,
and you're not clapping cuz you think
all right.
Are we dumb? I didn't know that. That's
not [laughter]
That's not good." No, I don't remember
where we parked the car, actually.
That's not
Date smarter if you possibly can. And I
say smart and not clever because there's
a big difference between smart people
and clever people. There are a couple of
people nodding out there who've dated
clever people before. You know what I'm
talking right now if you're sitting
there and you're like, I'm not sure if
the person I'm with is smart or clever.
Well, they're clever. That's how
[laughter] that's how they work. But
it's just a totally different thing
between dating smart and clever people.
And it really comes out when you get
into any sort of argument. Like if I get
in an argument with my wife who's
smarter than me, it usually plays out
just kind of like, "Hey, you know what,
sweetie? I think I'm right." And then
she'll say, "No, actually, I think I'm
right." And I'll be like, "Fine. You
tell me why you think you're right." And
then she'll list a bunch of facts
and I'll say, "But that's it." And it's
um [laughter]
it's over. It's really quick, but
there's a lot of time left in the
evening to get more things wrong, which
is [laughter]
very helpful.
But clever people, it's a totally
different thing. It's a totally
different way of arguing because clever
people don't use facts. They just bring
up times that you've been wrong in the
past to completely invalidate your
argument. Anybody had experience with
this before? It's like trying to date a
negative political attack ad
against you. [laughter]
You know what I'm saying? So, when you
come out and you're like, "Hey,
sweetheart. I'm going to uh going to go
hang out with the guys tonight, watch
the game. I'm pretty sure I told you
about this last week." Then she comes
back with, "Oh, really?"
Drew Bar says that he's pretty sure he
mentioned last week he was going out
with the guys tonight. But isn't this
also the same Drew Bar that was pretty
sure the movie started at 8:15 last
night? And we know how that one turned
out.
And isn't this the same Drew Bar that
was pretty sure he ordered more flea
medicine for the cats online? Wrong
again. [laughter]
Are we really going to trust a man who
doesn't even know what drawer the big
spoons go in? [laughter]
Don't this Thursday. Vote no on Drew
going out and having a good time with
his friends.
>> Cuz Drew Bar wrong on big spoons, wrong
on everything. [laughter]
[cheering and applause]
This brought to you by the woman who
knows where the big spoons go. That's
I know a lot of people feel pressure to
get married. We didn't really feel much
pressure. The only pressure I actually
felt was when I actually went to go shop
for the engagement ring. Uh because I'd
never been engagement ring shopping
before. The last time I even got a
little bit close, I ended up getting in
a fight with a girl I was dating. Uh it
was not even over buying the jewel. It
was just a jewelry commercial we saw on
TV. We were in kind of that weird sort
of where's this going kind of place and
then we were sitting on the couch
watching TV and one of those Debeers
Diamond commercials came on and it used
to end with a diamond is forever
and the girl I was dating looked over at
me and she was like you know a diamond
is forever.
[laughter]
I was like I know so is styrofoam
actually.
[cheering]
Why are you crying? Hold on a second.
I'm just saying it's a lot cheaper and
then you'd never lose your ring in the
pool. Think about that. Just [laughter]
a boat keychain. It just float.
I feel so sorry for guys when I see some
of these jewelry commercials because I
know that they're targeted just towards
guys and not towards women. They're
commercials that come on like during a
football game and a guy's like, "Oh,
that oh that must be what she wants.
I'll get I'll get her one of those. That
open heart whale tail necklace
[laughter]
thing that Dr. Quinn medicine woman is
selling. I don't know. I don't know if
it's a keychain or what, but I'll bet
she'd like it. [laughter]
The Pandora bracelet, the with the
little charms on it where there's a
woman at the party. You can tell so much
about my life by looking at my bracelet.
Look at this. See, you can tell I've
been to Paris. Here's the Eiffel Tower.
And I like horses cuz there's a horse
here. Here's the bottle of wine because
I'm bad at forming interpersonal
relationships.
[laughter]
Or that ad for the Levon Chocolate
Diamonds. You can't tell me that some
dude didn't get a bonus that year cuz I
guarantee you they were sitting around a
big boardroom beating and they were
like, "All right, item number one. What
do we do with all the ugly brown
diamonds?"
And one dude in the back was like,
"Ladies love chocolate." They're like,
"Whoa, where did that come from?"
[laughter] IS THAT PHIL? ALL RIGHT, PHIL
GETS A LEXUS THIS YEAR. Good for you,
Phil. [laughter]
Actually, even Lexus does a commercial
that feels like one of those
over-the-top jewelry ads. They do it
every year around Christmas time for
their big December to remember, their
big year end event. They have a car in
the driveway with a big bow on top of it
and a commercial. Husband and wife out
there. Merry Christmas. Oh, it's a car.
And they Oh, that's cool. I wish just
once they would zoom in on the house to
show the kids in the windows being like,
well, guess I'm not getting that bike
this year. All right,
that's not good. Dad messed up. I told
you this isn't good for us. I was
getting out of this one.
I love being married though. I love
living with a woman. It's great. I don't
run out of stuff anymore.
Especially in the bathroom. And guys who
live by themselves know that's a problem
sometimes. Some sometimes you'll just
get in the shower in the morning be
like, there's no soap in here.
I'm fresh out of ideas. All right.
[laughter]
I'll just turn the water up hotter, I
guess. Yes.
Scrub really hard with alofa. You know,
my wife will buy multiple bottles of
shampoo at a time. It's a brilliant
idea. It is never crossed my mind at
all. I buy one one bottle of shampoo and
then when it gets to the end, unscrew
the top, hold it up to the shower.
Oh, you people have all done this. You
know what I'm talking little little
shampoo cocktail for yourself there.
All right. This is going to be the same
thing. Wow, that goes right in the eyes.
Look at that.
Maybe if you're like me, you dive into
the sink. You bust out the hotel
miniatures you've been stealing for the
past 15 years. All right, Candlewood
Sweets. What do we got today? All right,
blueberry. All right. [laughter]
I wouldn't normally use blueberry
shampoo, but I don't really have much of
an option.
And this is uh this is moisturizer.
Yuck. Hey,
I'm just going to be shiny all day. All
right, [laughter]
my wife and I moved into an apartment
that has two bathrooms, which I think
already just adds another 5 years to our
marriage. The fact that we don't have to
compete for a shower in the morning, and
we never take a shower together. Uh I
think some people think that's strange,
but honestly, it's just not practical
for us because when you first get
together with somebody, the idea of
taking a shower together sounds awesome.
If a woman's like, "Hey, I'm uh I'm
thinking about taking a shower."
Hopefully not in that voice. I should
point that out. That's going
to take a shower.
[laughter]
It's very appealing when you first get
together, though.
But any guy here that lives with a woman
knows that if you try and take a shower
together, odds are it's just going to
turn into you standing in the back for
about six minutes just
[laughter]
freezing back here. It's really cold. I
I can see it's hot up there. I can I can
see the steam. That's where I stand when
I take a shower, quite frankly. But
sweet. What happens though is the water
hits the top of your forehead and it
comes off as this cool fine mist and
that's all I get to work with. I get a
little produce shower. This is going to
take forever for me to get clean. Is it
my turn? All right. Fantastic. Cool. All
right. Here we go. We're on different
rinsing cycles. I don't want to mess
that up. Cool. I don't recognize any of
these B. Oh, you got to condition three
times. All right. Let me get right back
there. That was warm. Okay. [laughter]
This is uh boring. Actually, this I know
you're naked. That's cool. But if I knew
it's going to go this long, I would have
put my Kindle in a ziplo or something.
[laughter]
Are you Are YOU GETTING OUT? YOU'RE
GETTING OUT. COOL. YEAH, take both
towels. I don't I don't need both
towels, you know. Just We are out of hot
water, though, sweetheart. So, it's all
right. I'll just smell today. That's
fine.
I like our apartment. I like our
bathrooms. I have one gripe with our
bathroom, though, and it's the way that
it's set up. It's configured in such a
way where when you're standing in the
shower and you pull back on the shower
curtain, that main mirror is right
there.
And I'm not usually ready for that.
Like cuz normally if you're going to be
naked in front of a mirror, you kind of
psych yourself up a little bit, right?
You just be like, "All right, here comes
the mirror." [laughter]
You just flex the whole time you're in
front. Hey, you look pretty good today.
All right, just brush your teeth. There
we go. I'm putting my contact lens. All
right. [laughter] All right. You deserve
a pizza. Good for you. All right.
Somehow I forget every morning. I get
done with my shower. I turn off the
water, put my shampoo back, pull back
the shower curtain. I'd rather see a
puma in my bathroom than my naked,
disappointed, foggy self looking back at
me. [laughter]
Also, whoever it was that designed the
mirror to go down to here, we need to
talk because I've also discovered that
kind of my personal self-confidence in
my body is directly correlated to
wherever I wrap the towel around myself.
Like some dudes wrap it around here.
Stop it. Uh I like to go like right over
If I could wrap it around my neck,
that'd be make like a Kate poncho kind
of thing. That's [laughter] That's the
look I'd like.
My wife and I, we did try and get into
good shape for uh for our wedding. I've
never really never really had kind of a
a physical fitness goal to get towards.
Uh my wife does like to watch a lot of
soccer and [laughter]
and if you've ever watched soccer with a
girl, it is cuz those players are
ridiculously
good-looking uh and in tremendous shape.
And it's actually kind of like a level
of physical fitness that I feel like
anybody can attain, which I think is why
it's kind of even harder to watch. Like
I don't want to just see a whole bunch
of me if I actually applied myself like
this. [laughter]
I think that's part of the reason why
soccer has had trouble catching on in
the US the way it has with the rest of
the world is that we like our athletes
to just be genetic freaks. So that when
we watch it, we're like, "Well, I'll
never be that big or that muscular, so I
don't even have to try." Awesome.
[laughter]
Where's that cheese blizzard I was
working on?
And you can actually even watch other
sporting events with a girl and feel
okay about yourself. If you can watch
the NFL and be like, "Sweetheart, would
you like it if I was, you know, 66 250
lbs? Would you even want that?"
>> No, that's too big. That's No, I
That's too many muscles. We couldn't fit
on the couch for me.
Watch Grace and Adam. You'd scare the
cat.
[laughter] You watch the NBA with a
girl. Sweet. Would you like it if I was,
you know, 6'8 like that guy? Would you
want that? No, that's too tall. It's too
tall. We don't mind cuz we like to spoon
and that just be like be like a spoon
and a and a ladle. Just
[laughter]
But if you try watching soccer with a
girl, you're like, "Sweetheart, would
you like it if I was, you know, 6% body
fat,
had a fauxhawk,
[laughter] spoke Italian,
sweetie?
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, I really would actually.
[laughter]
I'm just saying you can do it. You guys
are the same height and he's [laughter]
he's like 6 years older than you.
He looks great. No, finish your burrito.
I'm glad you like burritos. I'm just
just saying he probably doesn't get
winded when we make out. So, [laughter]
it's fair point. That's a good point.
I do uh do belong to a gym somewhere.
I'm pretty sure. Not quite sure where it
is. Uh $16 keeps coming out of my
checking account every month. I haven't
really tracked it down yet, but I did
used to belong to one gym where kind of
one of the cool perks was that every
month you got one free personal training
session with one of their big trainers,
which is cool cuz I don't know anything
about working out. But it always would
frustrate me because I would always get
one of these huge hulking dudes who
would never really convey how difficult
it was the exercise that they were going
to have you do. They would just kind of
assume you were in fantastic shape. This
dude would be like, "All right, man.
Here's what you're going to do. You're
going to come over. You're going to sit
down on this thing. You're going to grab
these two bars and just start pulling
them into your chest. Just boom, boom,
boom, boom, boom. See, it's like a
metronome. I'm not even thinking about
the boom. I'm just not even thinking
about the breathing. I'm just thinking
about the plates going up and boom boom
boom. All right, man. You get down
there. You can throw down about 25 of
those. I'm like, sweet. Okay. So, I get
down. I grab. All right. That's
Did you TAKE THE SAFETY OFF ON THAT? CUZ
THAT'S um it's not moot. I'll try to
Okay, so I get down.
Yeah. Okay. [laughter]
See, there was like a boom, but it was
like here. And I don't I don't want to
press my luck on that. Maybe we'll just
skip that for now. Where are the
showers? Just out of curiosity, if you
were to point in a direction where
[laughter]
my whole level of personal fitness was
uh my my goal was actually set for me
kind of by my wife. She uh she bought me
underwear for Valentine's Day one year.
Didn't know you could do that. That's
And she got me boxer briefs, which
personally I can't buy for myself. I I
usually feel worse about myself when I
see the dude on the packaging.
Do you guys know that guy? The guy with
like the He's got like the He-Man abs
and like a papaya shoved down the front.
[laughter]
So, he's got that cocky look on his face
like, "Are we filming? [laughter]
I'm not even flexing. I just wake up
like this.
I open them up and she's like, "Go
ahead, try them on." I was like, "Okay."
I tried them on. I was looking at the
box like, "Not even close.
Not I think these are broken, sweetie."
They are comfortable though. I've
totally converted. I love boxer briefs
now. Uh, and guys, if you're thinking
about making the switch, couple of words
of warning. First of all, never wash
them in hot water. Uh, or dry them on
the high setting on your dryer. I have a
couple of pairs of those where my butt
hangs out the bottom a little bit. Uh, I
look like a Hooters waitress when I walk
around the house.
It's not even a special occasion kind of
thing. It's not
Here's another thing to look for, and I
don't think this occurred to my wife at
all, but make sure they have a fly on
them. Seriously, they sell underwear for
men that doesn't have the little door in
the front. I don't I don't know who
they're for. Mannequins, Lego people.
I'm not quite sure, but [laughter]
I didn't realize that that was the pair
that I had on until I was in a public
restroom and I rolled up to a
[laughter]
not panic here. This [laughter]
some sort of release latch or some sort
of
a buttonfly kind of what what am I
wearing is Oh, hold on a second.
[laughter]
Nope, not on backwards. That was That
was my last kiss.
Finally, after a couple minutes, I was
like, you know what? Screw it. Let's
pretend I'm six. I pulled my pants all
the way down. Just
There we go. That's nice. That's breezy.
Why did I stop doing this? This is very
comfortable. Hey, what's up, dude? I'm
sorry. I didn't There's no door. I had
to pull him all the way down. It feels
nice. No, I don't want any money. Thank
you. I uh [laughter]
just not allowed to go back to that
Target in particular, which makes a lot
of sense. So,
my wife and I are trying to be uh trying
to be pretty healthy. We uh last year we
decided to go gluten-free
uh because we we like food uh but we we
wanted to pay more for it.
Was goal number one. We wanted to get
less of it
and we wanted it not to taste as good.
[laughter]
So far we're batting a thousand on that
one.
And you don't realize what an important
role gluten plays in some foods. Like
cornbread, for example, is not the most
structurally sound food to begin with.
And then we got some gluten-free
cornbread, which was like trying to eat
a sand castle.
Like you take one bite into it, just all
goes on. That's how it looked when it
came out of the box. Look at that.
You do find a lot more gluten-free food
at other places, though. And
particularly in Seattle, where I'm from,
it starts to kind of starting to spread
out a little bit. You don't have to go
to You don't have to go to Whole Foods,
which is good cuz I can't afford Whole
Foods. Not yet. I keep checking every
once in a while. Like, I keep checking
it out. Every once in a while, I'll step
in. I'm like, "Nope, not yet." Okay.
It's [laughter]
too nice. Too fancy. In particular, the
produce section. I feel like I always
walk into first and it looks like
nobody's ever bought anything in the
produce section at Whole Foods. It's
these perfect pyramids of fruit and
vegetables and like if somebody does buy
one, a guy has to run out from the back
and put another one out there. Like ball
boys at a tennis match, they're just
sitting THERE JUST SOMEBODY BOUGHT AN
APPLE.
[laughter]
>> [applause]
>> That's not an omen or anything, right?
That's not
[laughter]
cool.
You guys can edit that out, right?
[laughter]
Oh, goodness.
The most embarrassing thing for me
whenever I go to a Whole Foods is
discovering a new fruit or vegetable
I've never heard of before. That's
embarrassing for me when I'm just
looking around. I'm like, I what? I
don't. Then I have to ask one of the
stock boys, "Excuse me, I'm sorry. I've
never I've never heard of this before.
What is that?" The guy's like, "Are you
telling me you've never had a Puma
Renew?"
>> [laughter]
>> IT'S LIKE IF YOU COMBINE TOGETHER quinoa
and a date and uh it'll annihilate your
colon. Clear out your weekend actually
cuz they're on sale today. $27 a pound.
That's pretty good price for the Puma
Reno thing. [laughter]
Like I mentioned, I do live in Seattle,
which is a good place to be kind of
gluten-free and kind of crunchy and
such. We uh crunchy. It's a good word.
You know, we we like our healthy food.
We don't have a lot of uh we have a lot
of rain, not a lot of sun. Obvious.
I'm starting to the point where I just
don't even like the sun anymore because
I never tan. That like that would be
great if that could happen. I just go
white burn peel. That's all that's all
that I get. I don't know. [laughter] A
sunburn more than anything now is just
embarrassing because I feel like when
you have a sunburn, it's basically just
wearing a sign around your neck that
says, "Hey, I I have no idea how the sun
works." I [laughter]
35 years later, big ball of light. Go
figure. I
And I'm glad I'm married cuz it's hard
to pick up on ladies when you're peeling
and you basically have the last form of
leprosy left on the planet. Hey, where
you going? Here, take a piece of me with
you.
Sun seems to take people by surprise up
in the Seattle area. I can't tell you
how many times at the beginning of the
summer people will come up to you and
start conversations being like, "Hey,
it's staying light so much later."
Have you noticed that? Like it's been
getting dark at 9:15 and then like 2
weeks ago it was getting dark at 8:45.
I'm like, "Well, yeah, this happened
last year. You know, I had a friend of
mine come up to me the other day. He's
like, "Dude, this sucks. I guess boating
season's almost over." I was like,
"Well, you obviously have much more
money than I do. I have never I've never
noticed boating season really. I don't I
don't even know what boating season is
to be honest. I don't know if you stop
hunting them at some point or if they're
under 20 ft, you throw it back. I don't
know. [laughter]
I would like to have a boat. That sounds
nice." There are people a lot of money
up in Seattle now with Amazon and
Microsoft. People are getting big boats,
getting yachts. Uh I was recently
introduced to the term mega yacht.
Somebody had parked one off the shore of
Seattle. It was a mega yacht that was
worth $110 million,
right? You can't even wrap your brain
around that. However, I think the most
fascinating part of it was that just to
fill it with fuel costs $400,000,
right? Cuz I I' I've been on a boat
before when it's pulled up to like one
of those little gas docks. You can't do
that with that sort of just pull up
there. Hey, what's up? How's it going,
man? Cool. You got gas?
Sweet. I'm going to need all your gas.
[laughter]
All the Do you have friends with gas?
Call them, too. I'm going to need all
the gas you have. Do I press debit? How
does this work?
Just it's $400,000. You can't negotiate.
I have gold. Will you take gold? I just
just have a big bag of gold. That's what
I You don't take gold, but you take
discover. That's weird. Okay.
I feel like half the appeal of getting a
boat is just coming up with the cool
name to go with it. And I feel like
especially with yachts and sailboats,
they always have these really rich
sounding names. Those things like loving
life, ain't things grand.
That's cool. I want to try that with my
car. Just Yeah. Everybody pile into the
should have tried harder. That's mine.
[laughter]
Should have tried harder, too. Actually,
the last car was stolen. [laughter]
That was a new experience that I had to
deal with last year. My car was stolen.
I don't know if anybody's ever had their
car stolen before. Uh, I didn't love my
car. I was also not done using it.
[laughter]
More than like seriously, more than
anything, it was just a massive
inconvenience. I came out came out of my
apartment building one morning, cup of
coffee, it was just street parking. Came
over and it was just car car
no car.
>> [laughter]
>> no broken glass in the ground or
anything. And I was like, "Huh,
I totally forgot where I parked my car.
That's absolutely amazing." [laughter]
Cuz you don't just default to evil or
anything. You just You're like, "No, I'm
an idiot. I probably forgot where I
parked it." Walked around the whole
block. Chocolate myself. It's going to
be so funny where I found my car. It's
going to be hilarious. I make a whole
loop, come back around. I was like,
"Yeah, all right. Now I need to make a
phone call apparently." [laughter]
And there was a part of me that thought,
you know what, maybe my car was towed
because my car had been towed before. I
had some parking tickets with the city
of Seattle. Uh I thought my parking
tickets were decent. Although, according
to the city, I also had several
outstanding parking tickets. So, not to
brag, but they uh they don't give those
out to anybody. So,
but it also didn't quite feel like my
car had been towed. Because normally
when your car gets towed, it's because
you left it somewhere you don't feel
100% about. Like maybe you're in a big
hurry to get somewhere. You get like the
last spot on the curb in front of like
the restaurant you're going to, but then
like the back third of your car is
hanging a little bit into the crosswalk
to the point where as you're walking
away, you're like,
I don't know if that's going to be
there. [laughter]
You say to your friends, guys, if you
don't mind, I'm just going to move my
car quickly. They're like, well, what
are they going to do? What are they
going to tow your car? and then your car
gets towed
and those people disappear. They will
not drive you to a toward later. So, I
called the police. Uh, actually, first I
called a buddy of mine who lived about a
block away whose car had been stolen a
month earlier. And I was like, "Hey,
dude. Uh, I think my car got stolen. You
just went through the whole thing. What
do I do?" He's like, "Ah, man. It's
terrible. Just call the police. They'll
start walking you through it and they'll
get in touch with your insurance and
everything." I was like, "All right."
He's like, "When do you think they stole
your car?" I was like, "I don't know,
like 2:00 in the morning or so." He's
like, "Gh, sucks. Don't you wish you
could have caught the people stealing
your car?"
Yeah. No, actually, not at all. You've
met me before. Like, what would you
imagine I have done? I just would have
walked out. Hey, [laughter]
THAT'S NOT YOURS. HEY. WOW, they're
stealing it faster now. All right, that
really bothered me.
So, I called the Seattle Police
Department. I said, "Uh, yes. I believe
my vehicle's been stolen." And they're
like, "Okay, what kind of car do you
have?" I was like, "I have a 1998 Honda
Civic." And [laughter]
people chuckling like, "Oh, I've stolen
one of those."
Do you have a Civic?
It's a very easy car to steal. I never
realized how easy it was to break into
except for one time I accidentally
bumped into it a little too hard and the
driver's side door opened and the engine
started [laughter]
which I think is a design flaw at some
point.
[laughter]
I called the police. I was like, "I have
a 98 Honda Civic." They laughed and then
[laughter] they're like, "Yeah, that's
gone. Uh, probably not going to get the
back. Just get in touch with your
insurance." So, I called my insurance
agency and they started walking me
through the process, asking me a lot of
questions about my car, about the
condition it was in to kind of determine
what the value was going to be. And my
car was not in great condition because
it had gotten to a point where I'd had
it ever since high school. And now it
was just about kind of getting from
point A to point B. It's not it's not
cool anymore. It's just your car. Like,
it gain a personality. I don't know if
anybody else named their car. I named my
car uh I named him Doug,
which I know is not a fancy kind of
name, but it fits cuz he had one
headlight that kind of looked off in
another. [laughter]
He just gave off this D kind of vibe
like it was just
but he had a lot of cracks and dents and
scratches and things just didn't look
very good. So, as this woman is asking
you all these questions, I figure she's
going to get to the end and be like,
"Okay, based on our calculations, we'll
be sending you
a bag of gummy bears. Just [laughter]
I didn't have high hopes. Somehow it got
to the very end and she said, "Okay,
based on our calculations, we're going
to be sending you a check for $4,200."
And I said, "Yep, that sounds And I hung
up [laughter]
really fast and
and I took the $4,200, combined it with
my wife's sterling credit history, and
together we got a new car, which was
great. Follow up on that story, about 8
months later, I got another call from
the Seattle Police Department, and they
said, "Hey, we've uh we've located your
vehicle." I was like, "Ah, that's okay.
I don't want you guys to go out of your
way or anything.
we've all kind of moved on. [laughter]
He was like, "No, it was an abandoned in
a neighborhood. We've toted it down near
the stadiums. You can go down and take a
look, see if any of your personal
effects are still there. Also, we've
been in touch with your insurance
agency. They're sending somebody down
there as well." And my first thought
was, "Oh, no. [laughter]
They're going to want some of that money
back." I guarantee there's going to be a
guy walking around my car with a
clipboard being like, "All right, whoa,
wait. We paid how much for this?" 4,200.
That was supposed to be $42, you guys.
Somebody moved a decibel point. That
headlight doesn't even look in the right
direction. I don't. [laughter]
But I went down. I saw this car. It was
sad. It was the car I had ever since
high school. It had been ripped apart.
And I, like I said, I didn't I didn't
take a lot of pride of ownership in my
car, but I didn't mind driving it around
except when I had to take it somewhere
nice. Then it definitely felt a little
bit awkward. Like I lived in LA for
about a year and a half. I was dating a
girl that lived in Seattle. She flew
down for the weekend. We decided to
drive down the coast. We went down to
Newport Beach. Really nice area. I got
us a Hotwire hotel cuz I'm classy.
Seriously, if you guys haven't done
Hotwire before, awesome deal. $100, get
to stay in like a five-star hotel that
you have no business being in, usually
while they're doing massive renovations.
They were tearing asbestous out of our
room while we were sleeping, but I was
like, "Hey, these sheets are soft." So,
[laughter]
but it was awkward cuz as we were
driving up to the hotel, it was one of
those ones that has that big sort of
roundabout kind of thing with like a
couple of fountains in the middle and
then off to the side they have that
special area where they park all the
super fancy cars. So, a lot of like
Maseratis and Porsches and Rolls-Royce.
And I'm just putt putting up the hill
and Doug. And [laughter] I turned to the
girl I was dating. I was like, "Sweetie,
I am not going to valet Doug here.
Right. I hope that's okay. I'll just
drop you off. You check in. I'll park
somewhere. I'll meet you in the lobby.
She's like, "Okay." So, we pull up to
the front. She gets out. The valet guy
hops out. He's like, "Hi there. Check it
in." I was like, "Yes, she is. Uh, I'm
not going to valet though. I I'll just
park myself somewhere." And the guy's
like, "Well, actually, we valet park all
the vehicles for everybody who's staying
here."
I was like, "Okay."
Then we both just sat there for a
second.
and he kind of was hesitant. And I swear
for a second I really thought he was
gonna say, "If you'd like, we could just
throw this away for you." Actually,
we have a pit in the back that's on
fire. We can just roll it on in. You can
you can pick up something new in town.
So, it's like, "Fine." I gave the guy my
keys, gave me a little piece of paper,
went checked in, spent the night. Next
day, came down, gave the guy my ticket
for him to bring my car around. And
while we were waiting, I turned to the
girl I was dating. I was like, you know
what would be hilarious? Like just to
kind of break the tension, what if when
he brings my car around, I just start
going nuts over the condition it's in?
[laughter]
Like, what if I just lose it? Just
pretend like I gave them a mint
condition 1998 Honda Civic. And then
when they roll Doug's sorry self around
the corner, I just go nuts. JUST BE
LIKE, "WHAT HAPPENED? YOU ONLY HAD THIS
FOR 12 HOURS. WHERE [screaming] DID ALL
THESE CRACKS AND DENTS COME FROM? THIS
RUST IS awfully advanced. I thought that
would be [laughter]
hilarious. Uh, unfortunately, before I
got a chance to say anything, I looked
in through the windshield and sitting on
the dash was this little piece of paper
with kind of the generic outline of a
car on it where they had marked up all
forms of previous damage so they
wouldn't be liable for it. I've never
felt worse for Doug in my entire life.
just all of his imperfections circled
and X's and somebody wrote should have
tried harder on the back.
But I love living in Seattle. It's my
home and this is the best job that I've
ever had. I will tell you though my
second favorite job I ever had which is
fairly unique. I used to work as a tour
guide at the Space Needle. Anybody with
this?
>> That's the appropriate level of
enthusiasm for the
>> [laughter]
>> It was not a great job. It really
wasn't. But I loved it cuz I used to
walk around the top and I got to answer
everybody's stupid questions that they
would ask when they got up there. That
was worth it for the job alone.
Especially from like people from the
Midwest that had never been above like
45 ft before that would just step OFF
THE ELEVATOR. HOLY COW. CAN I SEE
ALASKA? [laughter]
Can I see Alaska? Can I see Oregon? Can
I see Canada? Can I see Hawaii?
[laughter]
Can I see China? [laughter]
All true. I swear I There's no way I
will ever forget the dude who asked if
you could see China cuz he pointed as
well, which bothered me. I don't know
why. [laughter]
I SAY, "WOW, SAM, CAN I SEE? IS THAT
CHINA? CHINA?"
NO. [laughter]
NO, you cannot see China, sir. Not
today, at least. It's [laughter]
foggy.
People get up there. Hey, how do I get
down? [laughter]
How did you get up? [laughter]
People would point at the elevators. Is
the elevators go down?
No. [laughter]
No, they do not. Those are just our
upvaders, actually.
tell you how it works. They come up once
and we have to throw them away.
We are losing a lot of money on those.
You're right. As a matter of fact, if
you want to get down, there's a 500 foot
long fireman's pole that goes down the
middle. Chase your thighs really bad. We
take a picture at the bottom. It's
awesome. It's worth it. I had one story
[laughter] that beat everybody else's
there. And I promise I am not making
this up. This is absolutely true. I
couldn't make it up if I tried. One day
I'm standing in my little information
podium. This dude gets off the elevator,
smiles at me, waves, and then starts
walking around, reading all the little
facts on the walls, looking out the
windows, makes a full revolution, comes
back around, stops, looks really
confused, makes a beline for my podium,
and says, "Excuse me. Um, I've never
been to Seattle before, but um, I know
it's famous for the Space Needle.
I was just wondering if you could see it
from up here.
[laughter]
I said, "Well,
You're never going to believe this,
[laughter]
but as you may have noticed when you
were getting off the elevator, reading
the stuff on the walls, looking out the
windows,
[groaning]
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> They take it down in the winter, sir. Uh
it's uh this is a lot of fun to watch,
as a matter of fact. But right now,
you're in the world's tallest pepper
grinder. I think that's pretty cool as
well. So, you guys have been an awesome
audience. Thank you so much, ladies and
gentlemen. [cheering]
[music]
>> Good to see you all. Glad you all made
it through the quarantine. I hope uh
hope everybody had uh somebody to to
spend it with. I was excited about my uh
spending time with my wife. We're coming
up on five years this fall. [cheering]
[applause]
Pretty exciting. Six if you get out the
quarantine cuz I think that's two. You
think you count them for that's like the
gold ball at the end of Price is Right
or something. I don't [laughter]
And I think it was really important. I
mean a lot of people wonder like how do
you stay with somebody? We were in a
fairly small apartment. It's like, how
do you two manage not to get on each
other's nerves all the time? And I don't
want to say that the secret is the fact
that we're both somewhere on the ADD
spectrum. However, uh [laughter]
you really you your your house feels so
much bigger if you forget you live with
someone else. It's sort of a remarkable
thing. I
would forget often. I would walk out of
the kitchen, see my wife on the couch.
Oh, hey, how's it going? All right,
cool. Then 5 minutes later, I'd hear a
toilet flush like somebody broke into my
apartment.
Mhm. All right.
I'm glad though that before this whole
quarantine started that we were already
in a very good sort of secure place. We
were married. We were living together. I
know that there were a lot of couples
that kind of were advanced to that next
stage because of quarantine. And there
were some people who were not ready for
this at all. And I'm sure that there
were a handful of couples that broke up
over some very petty arguments. I
guarantee you somebody came home was
like, "Hey, you know what I noticed is
that um when you put your clothes away,
um you hung them on my hangers and then
you put them on my side of the closet."
So, uh yeah, we're done.
[laughter]
That's the straw that broke the camel's
back. I didn't see that coming, but um
[laughter] your stuff is in a box out in
the hallway. So,
but I think it was important though that
because we had already had conversations
about a lot of the little types of
things and usually with roommates, it's
she is my roommate. She's the cleanest,
best roommate I've ever had. She's the
only roommate I've had who I haven't had
to get into an argument with about
dishes, which is fun. I I thought I was
going to have one of those roommates
throughout the rest of my life. Always
just one person who didn't want to do
the dishes. One dude didn't want to do
the dishes, would leave dishes in his
room, even refused to buy dish soap like
to kind of chip. He's like, "You guys
are figured out. [laughter]
I don't know if anybody's ever had uh a
fly problem before. Um, and not just
flies, but where it's a fly problem to
that point where, and I'm not talking
about house flies, cuz house flies
everybody has. No matter how clean your
house is, you're going to wake up one
morning with just something buzzing the
tower around your, OH WOW. WHAT IS
THAT?
>> [laughter]
>> BIG JURASSIC Park bug. I need a
crossbow. What is
We have fruit flies. The little tiny
ones. You familiar with those? Camp out
in your sink like a little surprise
party.
[laughter]
Somebody puts a DISH IN THERE. SURPRISE.
HEY, YOU LIVE IN SQUALOR. [laughter]
I could hear them taunt me when I got
home from the grocery store. They'd be
like, "You bought a banana. [laughter]
I'm going to live the rest of my life on
that banana. I figured it until Tuesday.
That's all I got. But [laughter]
we would have friends that came over.
They would try and give us tips. They're
like, "Oh, you got flies? All right.
Here's what you do. You take a cup and
you pour some dish soap in there and
then they'll fly in and they'll die." I
was like, "Sweet, dude. If we had dish
soap, we wouldn't have flies in the
first place." [laughter]
Mike, you remember that? No dish soap.
Cool.
find out the only way to get rid of
fruit flies is to get one of those
little sticky nofly strips. Not a line.
That's a That's a classy purchase to
make. The ladies love to see that over
YOUR PLACE. OH, WOW. YOU COLLECT THINGS.
[laughter]
NO, I don't want to put my purse down
anywhere. [laughter]
It's frustrating how effective a no-fly
strip is because it's just a big sticky
smelly strip and you put it up there and
flies just immediately start landing all
over it. And I just was looking I was
like I almost started feeling bad when
you see one just going
it smells pretty good.
A lot of dead friends of mine over
there. [laughter]
I'm going to go real fast.
It's like driving around a McDonald's
with a bunch of bodies out front.
>> [laughter]
>> This is a lot of corpses, dude. I'm not
going to lie. That's uh
See? Oh, PRESSURIZED. [laughter]
We had a lot of flies. We also had a a
lot of spiders as well, which I live in
the Northwest, so we don't really have
the scary kinds of spiders, but there's
something about just spider leg movement
weirds me out. Even the daddy longlegs
would freak me out. And I I know that is
the the wussiest spider with no poison
whatsoever. But something about the leg
movement would just freak me out. That
go. Excuse me. Hi. Just don't uh don't
mind me. I'm just going to go behind
your dryer. See if [laughter] YOU
ANYTHING. WHAT? YOU NEVER clean back
here. Did you know that? Okay, let's
It's not a scary spider. The daddy
longlegs. There there are really
terrifying spiders. There's the black
widow and the brown recluse. In South
America, there is the Goliath bird
eating spider,
which I have to give it up to the
scientists for not even trying to come
up with a better name for that.
I just picture two British guys down in
the jungle. IT'S LIKE, OH, LOOK AT THIS.
New species of arachnid JUNKS AND THE
FRONT LEGS are a bit longer.
[laughter]
EATING A BIRD.
BIRD EATING SPIDER. I CALL DIPS ON THAT
ONE. THAT'S MINE. YOU CAN, you know, THE
PENGUIN EATING SCORPION THAT GOES. There
you go. That's fine. [laughter]
But it's nice to kind of be in a place
where now our house feels clean. Uh
because there's a there's a big sort of
change in overall expectations when you
get together with somebody. You should
have that conversation of like what does
what does clean look like for you?
Because everybody has their own
definition of what clean looks like.
[laughter] Varies from person to person.
I think a lot of times it's kind of
carried over from whatever cleanliness
of household you grew up in. So like I
know some people if you were to come
home and let's say the night before you
left out like a pizza box and a couple
of dishes in the sink and a couple of
cans out, you don't think anything of
it. Growing up, if I had come home to my
house and walked in the kitchen and seen
all of those items there, I then would
have called 911. Uh because my mother
has been kidnapped there.
There's no way she left the house of her
own accord with those things left
behind. So, [laughter]
but it's important to have those
conversations about about cleanliness.
We've kind of gotten now to a point
where we're we're we're vacuum shopping.
Actually, I bought a new vacuum last
year uh that costs more than I spent on
video games in a year. So, I got my
adult merit badge for that one, which
[laughter]
yeah, it feels good. [applause]
And I LIKE VACUUMING. I HONESTLY I have
to BE HONEST. I LIKE VACUUMING. I didn't
I didn't always I think I've just been
doing it for a long period of time that
I've gotten pretty good at it. And I'm
I'm also just I love vacuuming cuz I
love our vacuum now because it's not the
vacuum I had as a kid. And all the
vacuums that you had when you were five
or 6 years old were just incredibly
heavy and unwieldy and you were supposed
to do stairs with them even though they
couldn't go on stairs. They're just
Okay. I smell burnt carpet. That can't
be right, man.
I don't know who this Dyson dude is, but
that dude hated vacuuming growing up.
IT'S LIKE SO UNFIN. I DON'T KNOW IF
THAT'S what his accent is, but that's
what I've [laughter]
convinced myself of. At least
I got pretty good with vacuum cleaners.
I got good at fixing vacuum cleaners
because uh when I went to college uh in
my fraternity, we'd never had a new
vacuum cleaner. We just had like a
legion fleet of all the other old
vacuums that parents would give to us.
It was like setting it was like setting
a telling you telling somebody you like
sent the dog to a farm upstate. It's
like well we're going to send Hoover
away to the fraternity. [laughter]
But there's lots of long open hallways
there. Lots of new things for it to pick
up along the way. This is what it wants.
But we had to keep a whole bunch because
we would have a party fire up one of the
vacuums. We'd go about 20 ft and then
there would be a loud noise, some smoke
and it would stop working like, "Okay,
next one. All right, there we go."
[laughter]
When I moved out of college, I actually
really wanted to get a uh a Roomba.
Moved into a house with three other
guys. I was like, "Look, we don't like
vacuuming. Wouldn't a Roomba be kind of
like a perfect solution for us?" And
then I saw the size of a Roomba and I
was like, "That's not going to work.
That's too small. That thing will go
like three feet just
Okay, now I'm full. All right, I'll just
go back [laughter]
empty that out. Maybe I'll pick a new
direction this time. Okay.
Wow, that that felt above my pay grade.
Okay. All right.
[laughter]
All right.
I like our new vacuum, though. It's um
it's very nice. We actually I like our
vacuums so much that we actually have to
play a game to decide who gets to vacuum
the apartment. And uh my wife never wins
uh because I never let her play. I think
she'll do it wrong. I don't know if
that's
I think we're we're also starting to
look at a house, which is which is nice.
And I I'm I'm looking at that like well
that's a loud place to vacuum. I'm very
but I'm going to try and make sure that
we don't have one of those sort of like
shoes off only households or even if you
do at least have one of those rooms just
I don't want to have that room off to
the side that I feel like all my friends
had growing up where it was like well
this is our sitting room where none of
us sit.
I think we played a game of charades in
there in the 80s [laughter] actually.
those perfectly moan little kind of
carpet stripes there. I won't I'm I like
that. I like the pattern kind of thing.
I feel like vacuuming is a nice uh kind
of runup for mowing the lawn kind of
like if you can move, you know, make
some nice stripes kind of around that
would be that'd be cool. Uh I'm looking
forward to having a yard and doing some
yard work. I'm going to tell you right
now though, after spending some time in
the pandemic, um I am not going to
purchase a leaf blower.
Oh, the rest of you own leaf blowers.
Cuz if you do, we hate you. [laughter]
>> If you start up a leaf blower, I
guarantee you the only person who enjoys
that, the person who's using the leaf
blower. [laughter] Everybody else
around, their first thought is, "Really?
I hope he hurts himself." [laughter]
It's such an annoying sound. It's
like a little bit flat. It just kind It
kind of sounds like [laughter] like a
leaf blower answered the phone is
looking for a pen. Hang on.
I'm just
[laughter]
It's terrible sound cuz it's only one
sound. If they would release like three
blowers at a time and like each take a
different c like a different pitch and
make like a chord or something the whole
time. Oh, that sounds very nice
actually.
[laughter]
I didn't realize that we were actually
possibly going to be able to get a home.
Uh that my wife is tremendously good
with finances and everything like that.
I was not uh for a long time. I'm better
now, but I could definitely tell my wife
could tell that she was going to need to
do some of the heavy lifting like on we
hadn't been dating for too long and then
I got laid off and I said to her, I was
like, "Hey, sweetheart, don't worry.
I've been poor before. It's totally NOT
THAT BAD.
>> [laughter]
>> ONE OF THOSE PHRASES THAT WHEN YOU hear
the final word leave your mouth, you're
like, "That wasn't right."
That's not what you want to hear.
[laughter]
Because I always thought that I I would
be better at money. I think I'm a fairly
smart dude. I I remember early on when I
was young finding out what my IQ was and
then somebody else said to me, it's
like, "Hey, don't get don't get bogged
down in just one number. one number
doesn't dictate how smart you are or
[laughter]
how good you are at one thing. And then
then I learned what a credit score was.
And uh [laughter] I learned that's just
one number that really does dictate how
smart you are at one thing. And
[laughter]
and if you haven't been paying
attention, it's too late already. That's
I feel better about money stuff now. I
feel like I'm I'm a little bit more put
together. I once dated a girl that was
almost too good with money things at the
time for me. She was the actual branch
manager of a bank. So, she would come
home with financial problems. She'd be
like, "Ah, there's so many people out
there overdrawn." I'd have to be like,
[laughter]
"It's my people." actually that you're
talking about.
I didn't know anything about finance.
So, even on like our first dates, like
she would be telling me about her day
and using all kinds of banking terms,
APR, helock loans, refinancing. And I
had to finally stop her and be like,
"Hold on a second. I got to ask you one
question." [laughter] And I'm sure you
probably get this all the time, but
you did a deal on money. How does that
work? Do you
So, like a secret Jamba Juice menu that
you asked for and they gave you an extra
20 or is it
>> Did they give you a bag of the day old
money they were going to throw away? How
does that [laughter]
She said to me, "You know what your
problem is? You don't make a budget. You
should make a budget for yourself every
month." I was like, "I don't need to
make a budget, sweetie. It's gone every
month. That's
that's not a problem. It's not like I
can't spend it. It's just gone. AND UH
[applause]
>> it's not like I have a bunch left over.
I don't know where to invest or
anything. [laughter]
Just buy candy online. But but I did do
that. I did just buy candy online and
have it delivered, [laughter] which I
swear I could see like the six-year-old
version of myself be like, "Nice." So,
[laughter]
I also realized at some point I didn't
need to have a lot of money. I just
needed to have enough money so that I
went when I went to Subway and they
asked for my debit card, uh, my
butttocks wouldn't tighten up quite so
[laughter] much. Like, that's
that WAS MY GOAL BECAUSE HONESTLY, IT'S
KIND OF A SHADY sort of point when it
gets to that. Your food's already ready
by the time they ask for the payment. So
that can be kind of awkward if you're
not able to kind of produce anything
else, all I carry was just like cash,
debit card, credit card ship sailed a
long time ago. So this is kind of what I
finally I did come up with one idea. Uh
if your debit card is ever declined at a
subway, just pretend you are going
through a really messy breakup,
right? So then when they're like, "All
right, that'll be 7:48." You hand them
your debit card and they swipe it like,
"Okay, you know, that's uh that's
actually not going through." They'd be
like, "Really?
Unbelievable. Pull out your phone.
>> REALLY, KAREN? MY DEBIT CARD. ARE YOU
KIDDING ME? I'M SORRY. AND THEN WALK.
[laughter]
It's very awkward. They won't ask any
more questions, but uh you do need to
find a new subway. Uh [laughter]
but they're everywhere, so that's not
bad.
[laughter]
This has been a lot of fun. I uh I've
this is not the first time I had to
spend more time indoors than I had
planned on regarding the quarantine and
such. About 3 years ago, I was involved
in a really serious car accident uh up
in Seattle. I was crossing the street
and a guy at a pickup truck didn't see
me and hit me while going like 35 miles
an hour and then I woke up 3 days later
in the hospital which the only other
time that I had that experience of just
kind of like waking up somewhere that I
didn't remember. I usually felt the need
to apologize to people. It was
[laughter] I woke up I was like I'm
sorry why I'm here. I don't know. You
all look happy to see me. Okay, that's
great. No,
but I broke my knee. I broke my
shoulder. I had a uh I had an epidural
hematoma and I needed emergency brain
surgery, which um it kind of led me to
really figure out that your head itself
is kind of like an iPhone. Um you you
can open it and fix it, but you're
really not supposed to. YOU. [laughter]
They really don't want you to do that at
all [laughter]
because if you reach around to the back
of your head and you kind of feel right
around here, you you won't find a latch
for opening your head cuz it's not
there. It's not it's not supposed to be
there. Um, so now every time I go to the
doctor I have was had brain surgery at
the top of my chart and it kind of skews
off whatever flowchart they were going
to get to to ask me sort of like what
the problem was. Now I figured out that
really just my head is kind of like a
piece of electronics where you know when
you flip it over and there's that
sticker that's like warranty will be
void if the seal is broken. That's what
my head is now. It's a it's a void. It's
a warranty broken head and they're kind
of like we just we don't know what goes
on from there but
>> [laughter]
>> But and so it was an unfortunate thing,
but at the same time, I'm also very
lucky. That's all that I can really
think about all this because there's
there are a lot of reasons why I should
not be here at all. So the fact that I
was only a 15-minute ambulance ride to
the hospital. And as a matter of fact,
the doctor said to me, you know, if you
had been injured in this same injury
anywhere in the state of Washington, we
would have flown you to this hospital.
So the fact that you were only a short
ambulance ride is very lucky. And as a
matter of fact, on top of that, when I
was hit by the truck, I was thrown
towards the hospital. So [laughter]
I
I was on my way before I even landed. So
I thought that had to [laughter] be
worth something.
But it did give me a lot of appreciation
for some very kind of basic things in
life. I mean, uh, always give people
compliments if you can. You never know
when you won't get to say something nice
to somebody again. give people
compliments. Uh, if you can on a piece
of paper, I would highly recommend
writing down the names of like three
people you really trust and putting that
in your wallet because if you happen to
find yourself in the hospital, you might
be surrounded by some people you didn't
necessarily expect were going to be
there. So, yeah. So, I'd write down the
names of like three people you are
really comfortable showing your bare
buttocks to. Um, [laughter]
you're not going to be aware of
everything that happens and you might
run into somebody later and be like,
"Hey, WHY DON'T YOU COME SEE ME IN THE
HOSPITAL?" We did see you. We saw a lot
of you actually.
[snorts] I have to say I'm uh I love my
wife. She's uh she's wonderful. We we
also have found that it's a great it's a
great thing to have somebody there when
you get to sort of an awkward moment and
you feel like I don't know what I would
do just by myself here, but fortunately
I can kind of check in with this as a
person to be like this is nuts, right?
Like that's that's half of the joy. Like
for instance, I found that I cannot I'm
such a nice dude. I don't like to be in
uncomfortable situations where I have to
extricate myself. And the one that I've
not figured out how to get myself out of
is when you're in a situation and you're
about to buy something and then you find
out it is going to be way more than you
thought it was going to cost and finding
a way to just back out and be like, "I'm
sorry, no money." And then walk out like
it's
so I hadn't really been fully
experienced with this. Um, but then for
Christmas, my wife got me uh bought me a
couple of prints off of Etsy and she was
like, "Why don't we go and get them
framed?" Uh, and I don't know if
anybody's ever been to a framing store
before, but uh the whole feeling of
something about to cost a lot more than
you thought it was going to cost might
as well just say on the top of every
frame store. So, we I got these two
prints. They're kind of nice. They're
rolled up in a little tube. go into the
museum quality framing store where my
wife had purchased a $75 gift
certificate for $150 worth of museum
quality framing. I was like, "This
sounds great. We're going to have so
much money for leftover frames at the
end." [laughter]
So, we walk into the shop. Um, nobody
else in there. By the way, usually when
you walk into a frame store, nobody else
in the shop. You have the full undivided
attention of the person working there.
whatever sort of like pressure sensors
that they put into like jewelry stores,
they also put into frame stores. So if
you step on one, some dude walks out the
back, "Hi, [laughter] how you doing?"
He had his full undivided attention. Guy
comes out. He's like, "Hi. What are we
doing for you today?" I was like, "Well,
I got these two print things here." He's
like, "Oh, okay." He clears off his
whole table. He puts unrolls them, puts
like some leather weights on. They're
all fancy. That's cool. He's like, "So
cool. These are great. What are you uh
what are you thinking today?" I was
like, "Uh, flat. They're [laughter]
flat on a wall. That's pretty much
they're in a tube now [clears throat]
and that's not doing anything for
anything. So, [laughter]
what do you got? He's like, "Okay, well,
um, let's see. We We uh we can Let's
take a look here. We So, we've got this.
We've got Now, what kind of matting do
you want to go with these frames?" I was
like, "Uh, matting?" He was, "Oh, yeah.
Do you want to do like some matting?"
Yeah. Call out these. I was like, "Oh,
interesting." He's like, "Yeah, cuz this
this one is like brown and yellow." So,
we could do some matting with like this
dark green and kind of a forest color in
here. We could do then some yellow. I
was like, "You can do two mats." He's
like, "Oh, we can do two mats. We can do
we can do three mats." I WAS LIKE, "ALL
RIGHT, THIS IS COOL. I'M having fun at
the frame store." All right.
All right. Cool. And then he's like,
"What what do you want for uh what do
you think about the actual frame
themselves?" I was like, "I'm thinking
right angles." That just that's it. I
don't not
I'm not really too picky. He's like,
"Cuz we have all these various options
here." He turns around that big wall of
fancy boomerangs that they have at the
the [laughter] frame store. He's pulling
out like that little hook and getting
ones off the top. Just these ones are
nice. He lay them down here. Like, okay.
And then he says, "Uh, now um glass.
What do you want to do about glass?" I
was like, "That sounds nice. Let's do
it."
[laughter]
And he's like, "Cuz we have a couple of
different options for glass. We have uh
we have the regular glass and then we
also have the museum quality framing
glass." And I don't know if anybody's
ever seen the display uh between the
regular glass and the museum quality
glass. The regular glass looks like it's
just been cleaned with pizza. And it's
[laughter]
it's got scuffs and scratches. It looks
like it was trying to keep like a
Doberman back for a while or [laughter]
And then the museum quality glass. It
looks like it's made of an element you
never knew existed. It's just kind I
probably Oh, wow. That's actually hard.
I thought it was a force field kind of
thing, but there's there's something
there. I wouldn't have guessed. Okay.
All right. Well, I think we're going to
probably want to go with the museum
quality glass then. And so, by the way,
where are we at just from an, you know,
a price standpoint? He's like, "Okay,
well, let's see where we sit right
here." And he pulled out one of those
little solar powered
tabletop calculators. If you ever see
one of those come out somewhere, you're
going to pay a lot because that's a
thing's all off the books, no internet.
Yeah, it's going to be a lot of money.
So, he signed it up. He's like, "Okay,
let's see here." All right. So, for this
one here, for the Captain America one,
um, we're looking at 380.
Uh, that's if we go with the regular
glass or if we do the museum quality
last 420.
And I turned to my wife and I was like,
40 cents? That doesn't seem like such a
big deal. [laughter]
And then that moment I was like,
dollars?
No. [laughter]
And I remember it getting so hot in the
store. I was like, okay.
All right. So, wow. Okay. Well, first of
all, thank you for all the hard work
that you've done [laughter]
here, sir. Um, now, if I were to tell
you that, uh, I have a $150
Groupon, um, [laughter]
that I was hoping to exit the store
without having to pay any more money.
What would you say to that? He was like,
you don't you don't know anything about
the Groupon? I was like, yep. He's like,
"Okay." He just grabbed all the stuff
they've been working out and just kind
of shoved it all into the bin over on
the side and then reached under the
counter. Might as well just pull out a
box that said crap frames on them. He's
like, "All right, here we go. Let's see.
We could do this brown one here and then
we could do this silver." It's chipped.
All right. No, it's black one here. So,
brown and silver. You think of that?
Yeah. No adding. He's like, "No adding
regular glass." Like, oh, okay. So, as
he's finishing all this and tabulating
it up, it still cost me like an extra
$74 on top of all this to get these
things framed. Dennis, he's typing them
up, but he also was like, "Oh, quick
question. What is the approximate retail
value of this?" So, just we need to
ensure it for, you know, if it's damages
we're working on. I was like, "Uh-huh,
sweetie. What do you think?" 40 $40. I
think $40, I think, was the approximate
retail value. This is not like a piece
of Abraham Lincoln's hat or something
that I'm giving you that [laughter] I
need to be in tuned and lose sight or
anything.
And so as this guy is adding everything
up, I'm looking around the store and I
notice they have all these other framed
pieces of artwork that are larger and
cheaper than what I'm going to be
purchasing. So part of me was kind of
like, "HEY, CAN I JUST BUY ONE OF THESE
and you just cut up the raw goods and
that would just be enough for you?" And
apparently no. Uh and my other suspicion
is that all of these framed works that
are in these framing shops uh were
actually projects that somebody had
brought in and then when they showed up,
they were like, "Wait, YOU WON HOW MUCH
FOR IT? KEEP IT. And now you have so
many pictures of ducks, you'll never
know what to do with them all. So, you
guys have been a wonderful audience.
Thank you so much. [cheering]
[music]